env: load .env
env: export EXPO_PUBLIC_SUPABASE_URL EXPO_PUBLIC_SUPABASE_ANON_KEY
Running 17 checks on your project...
15/17 checks passed. 2 checks failed. Possible issues detected:
Use the --verbose flag to see more details about passed checks.

笨・Check dependencies for packages that should not be installed directly
The package "expo-modules-core" should not be installed directly in your project. You should instead use the exported API from the expo package.
Advice:
Remove these packages from your package.json.

笨・Check that required peer dependencies are installed
Missing peer dependency: react-native-worklets
Required by: react-native-reanimated
Advice:
Install missing required peer dependency with "npx expo install react-native-worklets"
Your app may crash outside of Expo Go without this dependency. Native module peer dependencies must be installed directly.

