env: load .env
env: export EXPO_PUBLIC_SUPABASE_URL EXPO_PUBLIC_SUPABASE_ANON_KEY
Running 17 checks on your project...
笨・Check package.json for common issues
笨・Check Expo config for common issues
笨・Check if the project meets version requirements for submission to app stores
笨・Check for lock file
笨・Check for issues with Metro config
笨・Check dependencies for packages that should not be installed directly
笨・Check for app config fields that may not be synced in a non-CNG project
笨・Check npm/yarn versions
笨・Check native tooling versions
笨・Check for common project setup issues
笨・Check that native modules do not use incompatible support packages
笨・Check Expo config (app.json/ app.config.js) schema
笨・Check that required peer dependencies are installed
笨・Check that no duplicate dependencies are installed
笨・Validate packages against React Native Directory package metadata
笨・Check that packages match versions required by installed Expo SDK
笨・Check for legacy global CLI installed locally

16/17 checks passed. 1 checks failed. Possible issues detected:

笨・Check that required peer dependencies are installed
Missing peer dependency: react-native-worklets
Required by: react-native-reanimated
Advice:
Install missing required peer dependency with "npx expo install react-native-worklets"
Your app may crash outside of Expo Go without this dependency. Native module peer dependencies must be installed directly.

